[
	{
		"category": "Food",
		"question": "Made with eggs, milk and sugar",
		"answer": "Leche Flan"
	},
	{
		"category": "Weather",
		"question": "Destructive winds",
		"answer": "Tornado"
	}, 
	{
		"category": "Education",
		"question": "Another term for tertiary education",
		"answer": "College"
	},
	{
		"category": "Science",
		"question": "Smallest visible particle",
		"answer": "Photon"
	},
	{
		"category": "Science",
		"question": "Is the sun a planet?",
		"answer": "No"
	},
	{
		"category": "Internet",
		"question": "Famous app made in 2005",
		"answer": "Youtube"
	},
	{
		"category": "Streets",
		"question": "Oldest Street in Cebu City",
		"answer": "Colon Street"
	},
	{
		"category": "Anime",
		"question": "Anime that has the character Goku",
		"answer": "Dragon Ball"
	},
	{
		"category": "History",
		"question": "Number of years the Spaniards colonized the Philippines",
		"answer": "333 years"
	},
	{
		"category": "Internet",
		"question": "Most used social media app in the Philippines",
		"answer": "Facebook"
	},
	{
		"category": "Sport",
		"question": "Most famous sport in the Philippines",
		"answer": "Basketball"
	},
	{
		"category": "Science",
		"question": "Most important organ in the body",
		"answer": "Brain"
	},
	{
		"category": "Science",
		"question": "Largest body of water",
		"answer": "Ocean"
	},
	{
		"category": "Superhero",
		"question": "Who is Tony Stark?",
		"answer": "Iron Man"
	},
	{
		"category": "Countries",
		"question": "Capital City of the Philippines",
		"answer": "Manila"
	},
	{
		"category": "Countries",
		"question": "Capital City of America",
		"answer": "Washington DC"
	},
	{
		"category": "Animals",
		"question": "Man's Bestfriend",
		"answer": "Dog"
	},
	{
		"category": "Animals",
		"question": "Largest Reptile",
		"answer": "Crocodile"
	},
	{
		"category": "Movie",
		"question": "Filipina singer who was in Mulan",
		"answer": "Lea Salonga"
	},
	{
		"category": "Movie",
		"question": "Green ogre, friend of Donkey, husband of Fiona",
		"answer": "Shrek"
	},
	{
		"category": "Actors/Actresses",
		"question": "Famous Chinese Actor who did his own stunts",
		"answer": "Jackie Chan"
	},
	{
		"category": "Internet",
		"question": "Most famous search engine",
		"answer": "Google"
	},
	{
		"category": "Superhero",
		"question": "What superhero group/team was Batman in",
		"answer": "Justice League"
	},
	{
		"category": "Cartoon",
		"question": "Famous cartoon duo that hates each other",
		"answer": "Tom and Jerry"
	},
	{
		"category": "Sport",
		"question": "Biggest sport event in the world",
		"answer": "Olympics"
	},
	{
		"category": "Math",
		"question": "5 * 5 + (6 + 2) + (12 - (12 / 2))",
		"answer": "39"
	},
	{
		"category": "Movie",
		"question": "Museum comes alive at night",
		"answer": "Night at the Museum"
	},
	{
		"category": "Actors/Actresses",
		"question": "Main actor in the movie Johnny English",
		"answer": "Rowan Atkinson"
	},
	{
		"category": "Internet",
		"question": "Creator of Facebook",
		"answer": "Mark Zuckerberg"
	},
	{
		"category": "Sport",
		"question": "Famous Boxer in the Philippines",
		"answer": "Manny Pacquiao"
	},
	{
		"category": "Video Game",
		"question": "His brother is Luigi",
		"answer": "Mario"
	},
	{
		"category": "Countries",
		"question": "Capital City of Thailand",
		"answer": "Bangkok"
	},
	{
		"category": "Actors/Actresses",
		"question": "Main actor of I Am Legend",
		"answer": "Will Smith"
	},
	{
		"category": "Food",
		"question": "Made with chicken, soy sauce and garlic",
		"answer": "Chicken Adobo"
	},
	{
		"category": "Science",
		"question": "Smallest unit of matter",
		"answer": "Atom"
	},
	{
		"category": "Movie",
		"question": "Disney princess that died eating an apple",
		"answer": "Snow White"
	},
	{
		"category": "Movie",
		"question": "Kid raised by gorillas and monkeys",
		"answer": "Tarzan"
	},
	{
		"category": "Countries",
		"question": "Capital City of Malaysia",
		"answer": "Kuala Lumpur"
	},
	{
		"category": "Language",
		"question": "English translation of 'kumakain'",
		"answer": "Eating"
	},
	{
		"category": "Color",
		"question": "Mixture of blue and yellow",
		"answer": "Green"
	},
	{
		"category": "History",
		"question": "A holiday every December 30",
		"answer": "Rizal Day"
	},
	{
		"category": "Countries",
		"question": "Capital City of Australia",
		"answer": "Canberra"
	},
	{
		"category": "Countries",
		"question": "Capital City of Canada",
		"answer": "Ottawa"
	},
	{
		"category": "Things",
		"question": "You twist it to open",
		"answer": "Doorknob"
	},
	{
		"category": "Actors/Actresses",
		"question": "Actor who played Mrs. Doubtfire",
		"answer": "Robin Williams"
	},
	{
		"category": "Science",
		"question": "Liquid to Solid is called",
		"answer": "Freezing"
	},
	{
		"category": "Things",
		"question": "Another term for automobile",
		"answer": "Vehicle"
	},
	{
		"category": "Actors/Actresses",
		"question": "Main actor in the movie Cast Away",
		"answer": "Tom Hanks"
	},
	{
		"category": "Animals",
		"question": "Felines are what animals?",
		"answer": "Cats"
	},
	{
		"category": "Things",
		"question": "It reflects light",
		"answer": "Mirror"
	},
	{
		"category": "Technology",
		"question": "AI means?",
		"answer": "Artificial Intelligence"
	},
	{
		"category": "Geography",
		"question": "How many continents are there?",
		"answer": "7"
	},
	{
		"category": "Technology",
		"question": "WiFi means?",
		"answer": "Wireless Fidelity"
	},
	{
		"category": "Geography",
		"question": "Longest river in the world",
		"answer": "Nile River"
	},
	{
		"category": "Music",
		"question": "What band was Freddie Mercury in?",
		"answer": "Queen"
	},
	{
		"category": "Science",
		"question": "Study of plants",
		"answer": "Botany"
	},
	{
		"category": "Animals",
		"question": "Most feared shark",
		"answer": "Great White Shark"
	},
	{
		"category": "Science",
		"question": "Mineral to strengthen bones",
		"answer": "Calcium"
	},
	{
		"category": "Movie",
		"question": "Robots that are cars",
		"answer": "Transformers"
	},
	{
		"category": "Movie",
		"question": "Giant gorilla",
		"answer": "King Kong"
	},
	{
		"category": "Superhero",
		"question": "He can grow big and grow small",
		"answer": "Antman"	
	}
]
